代表时间变异管理局
On behalf of the Time Variance Authority,
我以侵犯神圣时间线的罪名逮捕你
I hereby arrest you for crimes against the Sacred Timeline.
前情提要
很久以前  全知的时间守护者出现了
Long ago, the all-knowing Time-Keepers emerged,
创造并梳理了神圣时间线
creating and organizing the Sacred Timeline.
有时  像你这样的人会偏离道路
Sometimes, people like you veer off the path.
我们称这种人为时间异体
We call those Variants.
劳菲森  你是否认罪
Laufeyson, how do you plead?
对了  我是莫比乌斯特工
I'm Agent Mobius, by the way.
你在这里干多久了
How long have you been here?
我不知道  不好说
I don't know. It's hard to say,
时管局的时间流逝不一样
time passes differently here in the TVA.
你招摇卖弄
Now, you parade about
仿佛你们是宇宙力量的神圣仲裁者
as if you're the divine arbiters of power in the universe.
无限宝石
Infinity Stones?
有人用这些石头当镇纸
Some of the guys use 'em as paperweights.
这是宇宙里最强大的力量吗
Is this the greatest power in the universe?
我不能回去  对吧
I can't go back, can I?
我给不了你救赎
I can't offer you salvation,
但我也许可以给你更好的
but maybe I can offer you something better.
一名在逃时间异体一直在杀害我们的时间卫队
A fugitive Variant's been killing our Minutemen.
你们需要恶作剧之神协助你们阻止他
And you need the God of Mischief to help you stop him?
那为什么选我
Why me?
我们要抓捕的时间异体是
The Variant we're hunting is...
你
You.
人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译       恶作剧之草   杏仁斯嘉丽     Eunice   小酸奶!
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
时间轴    念念   树      后期     吉吉         校|监       草草
威斯康辛州  奥什科什
许个愿吧
Make a wish.
怎么回事
What's going on?
你们的衣着不对
You guys aren't dressed right.
我...那个...
I... So...
已找到时间异体  指挥官
Variant detected, Commander.
行动
Let's move.
我们有些人很当真的
Some of us need this, you know.
尚未发现关联能量  长官
No nexus energy yet, ma'am.
是陷阱  自己小心
It's a trap. Watch your backs!
各位老爷  女士  欢迎
My lords, my ladies, welcome
谢谢大家加入我们  来到城堡
and thank you for joining us, here at the castle.
请在座位上坐好
Please, settle into your seats
一场大战即将开始
for a great battle is about to commence.
奖品  是我们的公主
The prize? Our princess.
邪恶会胜利吗  还是我们会等来英雄
Will evil prevail, or are we holding out for a hero?
指挥官
Commander?
Where have all the good men gone And where are all the Gods?
Where's the streetwise Hercules to fight...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
玩玩
Having some fun.
Isn't there a white knight Upon a fiery steed?
Late at night, I toss and I turn And I dream of what I need
I need a hero
I'm holding out for a hero Till the end of the night
He's gotta be strong And he's gotta be fast
And he's gotta be fresh from the fight
I need a hero
行动清单  选择程序
I'm holding out for a hero 'Till the morning light
行动清单  时间门  选择  运行程序  清除缓存
时间门
He's gotta be sure and it's gotta be soon
And he's gotta be larger than life
I need a hero!
洛基
第一季 第二集
动力  性能  质量
好了  各位  我们来复习一下都学了什么
Okay, y'all, let's review what we've learned.
关联事件分支突破红线会发生什么
What happens when a nexus event branches past red line?
很糟的事
Very bad things.
得了  洛基  究竟是什么
Come on, Loki. What is it?
那时  时管局变不能重置该关联事件
It's when the TVA can no longer reset a nexus event.
好吗  无聊
Okay? Boring.
对了  那就会导致时间线毁灭
Right. And that would lead to the destruction of the timeline
以及我们所知的现实的崩坏
and the collapse of reality as we know it.
你听到了吗
Can you hear me?
你是录音  还是活物
Are you a recording? Or are you alive?
算是都是吧
Uh, sorta both.
小心点  怎么这么没礼貌
Watch it! Where's your manners?
别闹了
Quit it!
那可不好  混蛋
That is not nice. Jerk.
-你不能躲...  -训练得还顺利吗
- You can't hide... - Training goin' well?
-嗯  -那是我的摩托艇杂志吗
- Yeah. - Is that my jet ski magazine?
放下吧  做好准备
Put it down. Gear up.
发生了袭击  我们走
There's been an attack. Let's go.
穿上
Put it on.
很好  嗯  很帅
Good. Yeah. Smart.
位置  威斯康辛州  奥什科什
C20和她的团队在跳入
C-20 and her team went dark
1985年分支后不就便失联
shortly after they jumped into the 1985 branch.
所有迹象均表明再次发生了伏击
All signs point to another ambush.
我们已获取了足够多的即刻气场
We've grabbed enough temporal aura
可以知道那是我们找的洛基时间异体
to know it's our Loki Variant.
但是哪种洛基  仍不清楚
But which kind of Loki, remains unknown.
肯定是不怎么样的那种  我们说清楚
They're the lesser kind, to be clear.
给我看看你外套后面
Let me see the back of that jacket.
时间异体
真含蓄  好啊
Very subtle. Well done.
我不希望有人忘记你的身份
I don't want anybody out there to forget what you are.
你逮住一个杀人犯的唯一希望吗
Your only hope of capturing a murderer?
不  是一个宇宙错误
No. A cosmic mistake.
-够了  -真会说
- That's enough. - Lovely.
是这样的
Here's the deal.
我们进入时间分支后
When we get out on the branch,
可不单单是要找一个时间罪犯
we're not just looking for a Time Criminal.
而是要找一个洛基
We're looking for a Loki.
这家伙的一个异体
A variation of this guy.
这种人我们应该都很熟悉了
A type we should all be very familiar with,
因为时管局删除过很多这种人
because the TVA has pruned a lotta these guys,
洛基
几乎超过其他所有时间异体
almost more than any other Variant.
没有任何两个是一样的
And no two are alike.
虽然外表稍有变化  也有的变化很大
Slight differences in appearances, or not so slight.
洛基
能力也不一样  但其能力一般包括
Different powers, although, powers, generally include
变形  幻觉投射  还有我最喜欢的
shape-shifting, illusion-projection, and my favorite...
分身
Duplication-casting.
幻觉投射
Illusion-projection.
不  这两种能力其实完全不同
No, they're two completely different powers, actually.
怎么说
How?
幻觉投射需要
Illusion-projection involves
细致地描绘一个非己的幻象
depicting a detailed image from outside oneself,
在外部世界里可以观察到
which is perceptible in the external world,
而分身则要一丝不差地
whereas duplication-casting entails recreating
重现目前状况下的自己的身体
an exact facsimile of one's own body in its present circumstance,
相当于其分子结构的真实的全息镜像
which acts as a true holographic mirror of its molecular structure.
但你们已经知道了
But you already knew that.
好  别激动  我们知道了
Okay, take a breath. Noted.
我们分为两队
We're gonna break into two teams,
包括我和洛基教授
including myself and Professor Loki.
为什么
Why?
因为不管这个时间异体是谁
Because whoever this Variant is,
我们一直没能找到他
we haven't been able to find him.
所以我们叫上一位专家吧
So let's bring in an expert.
就是我
That's me.
-我有武器吗  -没有
- Do I get a weapon? - Nah.
我能恢复魔法  就没人担心这个吗
Well, I'll have my magic back. Is no one concerned about that?
-担心什么  -我背叛你
- Of what? - Me betraying you.
-不担心  -为什么
- No. - Why not?
你已经知道我们能抓住你
Because you already know that we can catch you.
背叛我们
And how's betraying us
怎么可能让你更接近时间守护者
gonna get you any closer to the Time-Keepers?
我可以见到时间守护者吗
An audience with the Time-Keepers is on the table?
保持专注
Keep that focus.
关联信号峰值已定位  长官
Apex of nexus signature located, ma'am.
我问问你
Let me ask you this,
我们怎么不穿回袭击发生前
why don't we just travel back to before the attack,
去时间异体刚到的时间
when the Variant first arrives?
关联事件会降低时间流稳定性
Nexus events destabilize the time flow.
这支时间分支仍在改变  发展
This branch is still changing and growing,
所以你得按实际时间到场
so you gotta show up in real time.
你到底看没看让你看的那些训练视频
Did you watch any of the training videos you were supposed to?
我已经尽量忍着看了
Well, as many as I could stand.
你们时管局的宣传片真让人厌倦
Your TVA propaganda is exhausting.
这个是干什么的
And what do these do?
重置设备  可删除一条分支时间线受影响的范围
Reset charges prune the affected radius of a branched timeline,
让时间治愈其伤口
allowing time to heal all its wounds.
对了  这听上去就像是用冠冕堂皇地方式
Which, by the way, sounds like a nice way
说销毁周围的一切
of saying disintegrate everything in its vicinity.
他掌握了
He's on it.
我看视频了
I watched the videos.
看了一些吧
I mean, some of them.
他还劫持人质了吗
So he's taking hostages now?
时间异体以前从未劫持过人质
The Variant's never taken a hostage before.
或许他行动升级了
Maybe he's upping his game.
或是他删了她
Or he pruned her.
一个洛基不可能偷袭C20
A Loki couldn't have gotten the jump on C-20.
我觉得你是低估了...
I think you underestimate, actually...
散开  找她
Fan out and search for her.
快点
And hurry up,
我们离红线只有三个单位了
because we're at three units until red line.
-走吧  她说得对  -走
- Let's go. She's right. - Come on.
等等
Wait...
如果你们出帐篷  会落得像他们一样
If you leave this tent, you'll end up like them.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
计谋
I see a scheme,
我在这计谋里看到了自己
and in that scheme, I see myself.
我们阿斯加德有句俗语
We have a saying in Asgard,
"见到狼的耳朵  狼的牙也不远了"
"Where there are wolf's ears, wolf's teeth are near."
就是说  要注意周边情况
It means to be aware of your surroundings.
这很荒唐  因为我的族人
Which is absurd, because my people are,
天性就是好骗的傻瓜
by nature, gullible fools.
而我  恶作剧之神
A trait that I, the God of Mischief,
光凭注意听  就能反复利用这个特征
exploited time and time again simply by listening.
我的牙很尖  但我的耳朵更尖
My teeth were sharp, but my ears even sharper.
我们要没时间了  莫比乌斯
We're running out of time, Mobius.
等一下  给他个机会
Hold it. Just give him a chance.
你让我想到了他们
You remind me of them.
时间变异管理局
The Time Variance Authority
和阿斯加德的神们都一样
and the gods of Asgard, one and the same.
因权力而迷醉  对真相视而不见
Drunk with power, blinded to the truth.
你们低估的人会吞噬你们
Those you underestimate will devour you.
你们低估我
You underestimate me,
你们也低估了这个不怎么样的洛基
just as you underestimate this lesser Loki.
所以  你们才一次次地步入狼口
Which is why, you walk into one wolf's mouth after another.
两个单位了  他在浪费我们的时间
Two units. He is wasting our time.
好了  洛基  长话短说
Okay. Come on, Loki, make a long story short.
我们得去找C20
We need to look for C-20.
那正是时间异体希望你们做的事
That's exactly what the Variant wants you to do.
这是陷阱  他在帐篷外等你们呢
It's a trap. He's waiting for you outside this tent.
要我去安装重置设备吗
Should I secure the reset charges?
不  他要的是我  我是他计划的关键
No. He wants me. I'm the key to his plan.
-他知道我比他强  -一个单位多了
- He knows that I'm stronger. - Almost one unit.
而且他认为我们联手
And he rightly believes that together
就能推翻时管局  这是对的
we can overthrow and rule the TVA.
但那不是我想要的  我有了新的目标
But that's not what I want. I have a new purpose.
我是神圣时间线的仆人
I'm a servant of the Sacred Timeline.
现在我了解了他的策略
And knowing what I now know about his tactics,
我可以把时间异体交给你们
I can deliver you the Variant,
但我需要保证
but I need assurances.
什么保证
Yeah?
保证我完成工作后
Assurances that I won't be completely disintegrated
不会马上被消灭
the moment the job has been done.
好吧
Right...
而且我们得马上去找时间守护者
And we'll need to speak to the Time-Keepers at once.
他们的危险比我们想的要大
They're in graver danger than we realized.
他在撒谎  在耍诡计
He's lying. Just playing games.
这里没人
There's no one out there.
重置时间线
Reset the timeline.
你刚刚真差点骗过了我
You had me for a second.
我的耳朵也很尖
My ears are sharp too.
时间线已重置
追踪者C20  失踪
只有我觉得这间办公室
Is it just me, or does this office
越来越堂皇了吗
keep getting better and better?
那个雪球你哪弄来的
Where'd you get that one, the snow globe?
我好喜欢
I love those.
我不记得拿过那个箱子回来
I don't remember bringing back that case.
你不是唯一为我工作的分析师
You're not the only analyst working for me.
但你觉得我是你最喜欢的那个吗
But, would you say, maybe, I'm your favorite one?
而且凭什么你可以留着所有
And why do you get to keep all the trophies
我办案的战利品
from my cases in here?
你就不觉得我会希望那双旱冰鞋
You don't think I'd love having that roller skate there
装点我的隔间吗
sprucing up my cubicle?
因为是我审批任务
Because I approve the missions.
有道理
Good point.
说起来  我们谈谈你刚搞砸的那个吧
Speaking of which, let's talk about the one you just botched.
我们谈话时  你可能需要这个
You might need this for our discussion.
希望是双份的
I hope it's a double.
这个时间异体
This Variant is...
"抗命  顽固  难以预料"
"Insubordinate, stubborn, unpredictable."
听上去像我认识的另一个人呢
Sounds like someone else I know.
我还在想  这听上去像我认识的一个人
I was just thinking it sounds like someone I know.
-莫比乌斯  -怎么了
- Mobius? - What?
本来就有杯痕了
Those rings were already there.
都是你留下的
And they're all from you.
或许是你另一个最喜欢的分析师留下的呢
Maybe it's from your other favorite analyst.
听着  萝雯娜  很抱歉
Listen, Ravonna, I'm sorry.
我知道
I realize that my, you know,
我对待这个洛基的方式很受争议  但是
methods with this Loki are controversial, but...
把一个危险时间异体带去出勤是有争议
Towing a dangerous Variant into the field is controversial.
对  今天的进展并没如我预料的那般好
Yeah, it didn't go exactly the way I wanted it to today,
但我们知道了一件事
but here's what we did find out.
那个时间异体喜欢拖时间
The Variant likes to stall for time,
最终  我们会发现另一个做同样的事
and, eventually, we'll catch the other one doing the same thing.
因为了解这个洛基  能帮我接近
Because understanding this Loki helps me get closer
我们在追的那个  是吧
to the one we're chasing. Right?
听着  我知道你喜欢坏掉的东西
Look, I know you have a soft spot for broken things.
-我才不呢  -你就是
- I don't think so. - Yes, you do.
但洛基是个邪恶  爱撒谎的祸害
But Loki is an evil, lying scourge.
他在神圣时间线上就是这样的角色
That is the part he plays on the Sacred Timeline.
或许他想变变呢
Maybe he wants to mix it up.
有时一直扮演一个角色令人厌烦
Sometimes you get tired of playing the same part.
有没有这个可能  他能改变
Is that possible? He can change?
除非时间守护者下令
Not unless the Time-Keepers decree it.
那便可能
And then, it shall be so.
那时间守护者怎么样了
And how are the old Time-Keepers?
你觉得呢
How do you think?
我不知道  因为我没见过他们
I don't know. 'Cause I've never met 'em.
幸好  不过  我不该这么说
Thankfully. Although, I shouldn't say that.
那个看上去...
That one looks...
时间守护者在密切关注此案的方方面面
The Time-Keepers are monitoring every aspect of this case.
我从未见过他们这么关切
I've never seen them so involved.
他们想要那个时间异体被抓住
They want that Variant caught.
我也是
So do I.
这是你跟这个洛基的最后机会了
And this is the last chance you're gonna get with this Loki.
好啊  我就需要一个机会
Great, that's all I need.
谢谢  萝·斯雷尔
Thank you, R Slayer.
富兰克林·罗斯福高中
我不记得这笔
I don't remember this.
这是你的另一个分析师的吧
This must be from that analyst you keep on the side.
保持专注
Stay focused.
眼睛看路
Eyes on the road.
莫比乌斯
Mobius?
我差点出门了
I was almost gone.
你真相信这个时间异体吗
You really believe in this Variant?
幸好  他的自信够我们俩人用了
Luckily, he believes in himself enough for the both of us.
如果不行  我亲手删了他
And, hey, if it doesn't work, I'll delete him myself.
他可傲慢了
He's really arrogant.
你可能在想  任务时发生了什么
You're probably wondering what happened out on the mission.
那是你抓洛基的第一课
That was your first lesson in catching a Loki.
料到可以预料的
Expect the expected.
做恶作剧之神的一半乐趣
See, half the fun of being a trickster
就在于知道大家都知道你是恶作剧之神
is knowing everyone knows you're a trickster, and then,
你的很多恶作剧就是利用了
many of your tricks can come from exploiting the fact
-你知道他们知道...  -闭嘴吧
- that you know that they know... - Okay. Just shut up!
拜托了  我在电梯里认识的那家伙呢
Please. What happened to the guy I met on the elevator?
那个不喜欢说话的  记得他吗
Who didn't like to talk. Remember him?
现在我不得不应付
Now I'm stuck with this guy
一个开口闭口都是洛基如何的话痨
who won't stop yacking away about what makes a Loki tick!
什么  那不正是我的作用吗
What? Isn't that precisely why I'm here?
不  我不在乎你是什么样的
No. I don't care what makes you tick.
你要帮我抓住那个更厉害的你自己
You're here to help me catch the superior version of yourself.
-仅此而已  -等等
- That's it! - Hang on.
"更厉害"这个词不对吧
I'm not sure "superior" is actually quite the right word.
看  出现了  就这个
See? There it is. Right there.
我愚蠢地认为
I believed, stupidly,
渴求认可的不安感
that insecure need for validation
能激励你找到那个杀人犯
would motivate you to find the killer.
不是因为你在乎时管局的任务  或想当英雄
Not 'cause you care about the TVA mission or bein' a hero,
而是因为你知道  这个时间异体
but because you know this Variant
比你厉害  而你受不了
is better than you and you can't take it.
好啊
Very nice.
你真以为可以操纵我
I mean, it is adorable that you think
真是可爱
you could possibly manipulate me.
我先了你十步
I'm ten steps ahead of you.
我一直在玩我自己的游戏
I've been playing a game of my own all along.
什么  施展魅力  好得到时间守护者的接见
What, charm your way in front of the Time-Keepers,
欺骗他们  然后控制时管局吗
hustle them, and seize control of the TVA?
差不多是这样吗
Am I getting warm?
史上最可靠的撒谎精的背叛
A double cross by history's most reliable liar.
好吧  那你为什么在里面替我做担保
Okay. Why are you in there sticking your neck out for me?
我给你两个选择
I'll give you two options,
随你信哪个都行
and you can believe whichever one you want.
A  因为我看到了一个在寒风中瑟瑟发抖的
A, because I see a scared little boy,
被吓坏的小男孩
shivering in the cold.
你不禁可怜那小冰孩
And you kinda feel bad for that ice runt.
B  我就是想抓住他
Or B, I just wanna catch this guy,
你想听什么  我就说什么
and I'll tell you whatever I need to tell you.
我不需要你的同情
I don't need your sympathy.
很好  因为我剩的不多了
Good, 'cause I'm runnin' out of it.
你想干什么  你接下来的操纵...
What's this? Next step of your manipulation...
不  这是最后一步  你的最后机会
This is the final step. Your last chance.
那我孤注一掷的最后机会需要什么
Oh, and what does my desperate last chance require?
工作
Work.
Work?
我需要你翻阅
I need you to go over each
时间异体的所有案卷
and every one of the Variant's case files,
然后给出你的...怎么说呢
and then, give me your... How do I put it?
你独特的洛基见解
Your unique Loki perspective.
谁知道呢  或许我们遗漏了什么
And who knows? Maybe there's something that we missed.
你们这么蠢  八成遗漏了很多
Well, you're idiots. I suspect you probably missed a lot.
所以幸好我还有你  还有一阵
That's why I'm lucky I got ya for a little bit longer.
你就坐在这张桌子上
Let me park ya at this desk.
别怕好好投入工作中
And don't be afraid to really lean into this work.
教你个好办法
Here's a good trick for you.
假装你的性命系于此
Pretend your life depends on it.
我去拿点零食
I'm gonna get a snack.
天啊
Oh, my goodness.
别告诉我时间异体伏击
Don't tell me the Variant ambushed
并杀害了又一支时间卫队
and killed another team of Minutemen.
还偷了他们的重置设备
And stole their reset charge as well.
你好
Hello?
需要帮助吗
Can I help you?
是  我在为时管局办要事
Yes. I'm on some important TVA business.
跟进一次外勤行动  你了解的
Follow-up to a field mission. You know how it goes.
我们在靠近峰值时红线了
We red lined near the apex, and...
那可不是好事
Well, it's never good.
我想调阅所有关于
Um, I'd like all files pertaining
时管局成立的档案  谢谢
to the creation of the TVA, please.
那是机密
Those are classified.
好吧  那我要所有
Okay. I'd like all files pertaining
关于时间初始的文件
to the beginning of time then.
-那是机密  -好  那时间终结呢
- Those are classified. - Okay, the end of time.
-那是机密  -好吧  我能调阅哪些文件
- Those are classified. - Okay, what files can I have?
阅读快乐
Happy reading.
时管局时间异体档案  洛基·劳菲森
阿斯加德的毁灭
七级天启事件  星球彻底毁灭
零异变能量
星球彻底毁灭
整个文明被毁灭
伤亡人数
零异变能量
我有发现
I found something.
不  我说了"档案没读完前  别来烦我"
No, I said, "Don't bother me until you've read all the files."
-我读完了  -所有吗
- I have. - Every file?
-是的  -跟时间异体有关的
- Yes. - Pertaining to the Variant?
答案不在档案里  在时间线上
The answer isn't in the files, it's on the timeline.
他躲在了天启里
He's hiding in apocalypses.
哪个天启
Which apocalypse?
历史上的哪个时间点  有好多天启呢
Any time in history? There's, like, a million of 'em.
诸神黄昏  你知道吗
Ragnarok. Are you familiar?
知道  阿斯加德和大部分臣民的毁灭
Yes. The destruction of Asgard and most of its people.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
是啊  很悲哀
Yes, very sad.
反正  我想到了件事
Anyway, it got me thinking...
讲
Go ahead.
关联事件
Nexus events
就是有人做了
happen when someone does something
他们不该做的事  是吧
they're not supposed to do, right?
要比那复杂些  但对
Well, it's a little more complicated, but, yeah.
很好  然后他们不该做的那件事
Great. And then that thing they're not supposed to do,
又连带出了各种其他
cascades into a whole range of other things
本不该发生的事
that aren't supposed to happen.
如此种种  直到最终
And so on and so forth, until eventually,
分支出了新时间线  是吧
a new timeline branches. Yes?
预定结果的混乱变化
Chaotic alterations of a predetermined outcome.
-对啊  那么假设  -你干什么
- Exactly. So, let's just say... - What are you doing?
-你的沙拉  是阿斯加德  -不
- ...your salad is Asgard in this scenario. - No.
那不是阿斯加德  是我的午餐
It's not Asgard, that's my lunch.
就是个比喻  等等的
It's a metaphor. Just hang in there.
-我还想吃沙拉呢  -我可以去阿斯加德
- I want that salad. - And I could go down to Asgard
赶在诸神黄昏导致它完全被摧毁之前
before Ragnarok causes its complete destruction
我可以随意做任何事
and I could do anything I wanted.
我可以  比如说
I could, let's say,
把绿巨人推下彩虹桥
push the Hulk off the Rainbow Bridge.
-他摔下去了  -盐是绿巨人吗
- There he goes. - The salt's Hulk?
我还可以...
And I could also...
在王宫纵火
Set fire to the palace.
不  住手  别给王宫纵火
No, just stop. Don't set fire to the palace.
我想做什么都行  那都不重要
I can do whatever I want to do, and it would never matter.
那不会有违钦定的时间线  因为
It wouldn't go against the dictates of the timeline because...
-不好意思  -天啊
- Excuse me? - Oh, god!
-是你  -见到你很高兴
- You! - Nice to see you.
借我用用  谢谢
I just need this for a second. Thanks.
因为  天启要来了
Because the apocalypse is coming.
诸神黄昏  不管我做什么
Ragnarok, Surtur will destroy Asgard
苏尔特尔都会毁灭阿斯加德
no matter what I do.
不  别
No, don't do...
-那是天启  -那是天启吗
- There's the apocalypse. - That's the apocalypse?
诸神黄昏毁灭了盐
Ragnarok obliterates the salt.
诸神黄昏
Ragnarok.
就是这样
There it is.
我在看什么
What am I lookin' at?
好吧  这个比喻很笨拙  但你明白我的意思吧
Okay, it was a clumsy metaphor. But you see what I mean.
无所谓  可以是任何一个天启
It doesn't matter. It could be any apocalypse.
可以是海啸  陨石
It could be a tidal wave. It could be a meteor.
火山爆发  超新星爆炸
It could be a volcano, a supernova.
如果你周边的一切
If everything and everyone around you
都注定马上要毁灭
is destined for imminent destruction,
那我说什么  做什么都无所谓了
then nothing that I say or do will matter,
因为时间线不会分支
because the timeline's not gonna branch.
因为它会被毁灭
'Cause it gets destroyed.
因此  时间异体可以藏在天启里
Hence, the Variant could be hiding in the apocalypse
随心所欲  我们也无从察觉
and do whatever he wants, and we wouldn't know!
不赖
Not bad.
带我去一场真天启  比如诸神黄昏
Take me to a real apocalypse, to Ragnarok,
我能让你看到
I'll show you.
好啊  那样你就能跑回家乡了吗  别想
Yeah. So you can run away back to your homeland? No.
不  我不回家  我们去哪都行
No, I'm not going home. We can go anywhere.
我都不会带你去散步
I'm not taking you for a stroll along the promenade,
别说去天启了
much less an apocalypse.
莫比乌斯  拜托
Oh, Mobius, come on!
能出什么岔子
What could possibly go wrong?
我们的理论已经过了检验
We gotta properly test this theory.
我说个有趣理论吧
Well, here's a fun theory.
你把我引去出外勤  然后背后捅我刀子
You lure me out into the field, and stab me in the back.
这个理论我可不想测试
And that's a theory I don't wanna test.
我绝不会从背后捅任何人刀子
I'd never stab anyone in the back.
那样背叛太无聊了
That's such a boring form of betrayal.
洛基  我研究过基本上你人生的每个时刻
Loki, I've studied almost every moment of your entire life.
你真的背后捅刀有50多次了
You've literally stabbed people in the back, like, 50 times.
那我再不会那么做了  都是窠臼了
Well, I'd never do it again, because it got old.
好吧
Okay.
这样吧  你不信任我  你信任这个
Okay, look, you don't trust me, you can trust one thing.
我喜欢说对
I love to be right.
意大利  庞贝
公元79年
-我们到了  -快开始了
- Here we go. - Shh, any minute now.
然后这座小镇就会被彻底毁灭
Until this entire town is wiped off the face of this planet.
想想看  那么多火山灰
Imagine. All that volcanic ash...
我知道  我们也别太乐呵了
I know. We don't want to get too giddy.
拜托  这多酷
Oh, come on! It's cool.
的确  但这样太不成体统
No, it is cool, but it's just not in good taste because...
他们反正也要死了
They're all gonna die anyway.
我知道  听好
I know. Now listen,
我会监视扫描器  看是否有异变能量
I'm gonna watch the TemPad for any variance energy.
-好  -我们得万分小心
- Okay. - Okay, because we gotta be careful.
如果你错了  你很可能是错的
If you're wrong, and there's a good chance you are,
那我们做的事  就可能引发严重分支
anything we do can create a huge branch.
莫比乌斯  你把世界末日都说得那么无聊
Oh, Mobius! You make even the end of the world sound boring.
听好了  我们本不该来的
Listen! Okay, we're not meant to be here.
-好吗  -好
- Okay? - Okay.
我们做的任何事  都可能影响历史进程
Anything we do can impact the course of history.
-你明白吗  -嗯
- Do you get that? - Yes. Yes.
所以我们先来些很小的扰动
So we're gonna start with very small disturbances.
-很小  -你会学鸟叫吗
- Very small. - Can you make bird noises?
鸟叫
Bird noises?
对  鸟叫  就那种啾啾声
Yeah. Bird noises. Like some, like, whooshing noises.
洛基  洛基
Loki! Loki!
走吧
Go!
自由了  我长角的朋友  你们自由了
Be free, my horned-friends, be free!
我叫洛基
我们是时间变异管理局的特工
我为大家带来了坏消息
你们所有人
你们都要死了
火山就要喷发了
我很清楚  因为我来自未来
我们是从未来来吧
We are from the future, right?
时管局算什么  它来自未来吧
What is the TVA? I mean, it's from the future.
听上去像  挺有未来感的
It sounds from the future. It's pretty future-y.
时间正好
Right on cue!
趁还有机会  享受你们的最后一餐吧
Enjoy your last meal while you can!
什么都不重要
Nothing matters!
所有一切都不会有后果
Nothing has any consequence!
趁你还有机会跳舞吧
Dance while you still can!
怎么样
How'd we do?
难以置信  异变能量为零
I don't believe it. Zero variance energy.
时间线并未分支
No branching in the timeline.
时管局绝不会知道我们来过
The TVA would never even know we were here.
如果是我  我就会藏在这样的地方
If it were me, this is where I would hide.
末日  时间异体一直在伏击我们的士兵后
Doomsdays. The Variant's been ambushing our soldiers
躲进末日里掩藏行踪
and hiding out in doomsdays to cover his tracks.
-不客气哦  -嗯
- You're welcome. - Yeah.
但这理论要想成立  这些灾难必须是
But in order for this theory to hold, the disasters have to be
自然的  突然的  毫无预警的  无人生还的
naturally-occurring, sudden, no warning, no survivors.
-能有多少这样的灾难  -我不知道
- How many of those disasters could there possibily be? - I don't know.
我们查查看
We're gonna find out.
来  我们走走
Come on, let's take a walk.
对了  你桌上的那本杂志
By the way, at your desk, that magazine?
嗯  摩托艇的那个吗
Yeah. The one on jet skis?
嗯
Yes.
你为什么有那个
Why do you have that?
因为那个很棒
Because they're awesome.
-大概是吧  -嗯
- I suppose they are. - Yeah.
有些东西...
You know, some things...
其实  历史上大部分东西都很蠢
Actually, most things in history are kinda dumb,
一切最终都会毁灭
and everything gets ruined eventually.
但1990年代初  在那么美好的一小段时光里
But in the early 1990s, for a brief, shining moment,
形态和功能完美的结合了
there was a beautiful union of form and function,
我们称之为摩托艇
which we call the jet ski,
任何讲理的人都不会有异议
and a reasonable man cannot differ.
你骑过吗
You ever been on one?
没有
No... No.
时管局特工在神圣时间线上骑摩托艇
I think a TVA agent showing up on a jet ski on the Sacred Timeline,
那肯定会制造分支
that would create a branch for sure.
但会很好玩的
It'd be fun, though.
是啊  会很好玩
Yeah, it'd be really fun.
那为什么要看呢
So, why read about them?
提醒我  我们在为何而战
Just helps remind me of what we're fighting for.
你真相信这些东西  是吗
I mean, you really believe in all this stuff, don't you?
我不去纠结"信不信"
I don't get hung up on, "Believe, not believe."
我就接受事实
I just accept what is.
-三只魔法蜥蜴  -是时间守护者
- Three magic lizards... - Time-Keepers.
-创造了时管局和它的所有员工  -对
- ...created the TVA, and everyone in it... - Right.
-包括你  -包括我
- ...including you? - Including me.
每次我开始钦佩你的聪明才智
You see, every time I start to admire your intelligence,
你就说这种话
you say something like that.
好吧  那是谁创造了你  洛基
Okay, who created you, Loki?
约顿海姆的一个冰巨人
A Frost Giant of Jotunheim.
谁养大了你
And who raised you?
阿斯加德的奥丁
Odin of Asgard.
奥丁  众神之父
Odin, God of the Heavens.
阿斯加德  群星之域  神秘国度
Asgard, mystical realm, beyond the stars.
-冰巨人  听听你在说什么  -那不一样
- Frost Giants. Listen to yourself... - It's not the same.
-那完全不一样  -不
- It's completely different. - No.
-这不是一回事  -其实就是一回事
- It's not the same. - It's exactly the same thing.
因为如果你仔细去想  我们都是哪来的
Because if you think too hard about where any of us came from,
我们究竟是谁  听上去都很荒唐
who we truly are, it sounds kinda ridiculous.
存在就是混乱
Existence is chaos.
一切都没道理  我们就会想办法去解释
Nothing makes any sense, so we try to make some sense of it.
我很幸运
And I'm just lucky that
我降生的混乱  给了我这一切
the chaos I emerged into gave me all this...
我的光辉使命
My own glorious purpose.
因为时管局是我的生命
'Cause the TVA is my life.
它是真的  因为我相信它
And it's real because I believe it's real.
好吧  你相信它是真的
Fair enough. You believe it's real.
对
Yeah.
所以一切都是既定的
So everything is written.
过去  现在  未来
Past, present, future.
根本不存在自由意志
There's no such thing as free will.
这么说过于简单了
Well, I mean, you know, it's an oversimplification...
那么事实上  可以说
So, in fact, in a way,
在时管局的你和我
you and I here at the TVA,
我们是唯一自由的人
we're the only ones who are actually free.
你想说什么  洛基
Where are you going with this, Loki?
那要怎么结束
How does it all end?
那还在研究
That's a work in progress.
那些懒惰的时间守护者  他们还等什么
Oh, those lazy Time-Keepers. What are they waiting for?
恰恰相反
Au contraire.
不  因为我们守护之前的发生的一切
No. Because while we protect what came before,
他们在自己的小房间里埋头苦干
they're toiling away in their chamber,
把尾声从无限的时间分支中解开
untangling the epilogue from its infinite branches.
这样啊  那等他们做完之后  会怎样呢
I see. So, when they're finished, what happens then?
我们也就忙完了
So are we.
不再有关联事件
No more nexus events.
只有秩序
Just order.
我们在时间的尽头和平相见
And we meet in peace at the end of time.
不错吧
Nice, right?
只有秩序
Only order?
没有混乱吗  听起来好无聊
No chaos? It sounds boring.
你肯定觉得无聊
I'm sure it does to you.
你说我是被吓坏的小男孩
You called me a scared little boy.
我用各种称呼叫过你
I called you a lotta things.
没错
You did.
但你错了
You're wrong, though.
我知道一些小孩不知道的道理
You see, I know something children don't.
什么道理
What's that?
没有真正的坏人
That no one bad is ever truly bad.
也没有真正的好人
And no one good is ever truly good.
被吓坏的小男孩
Scared little boy.
是啊  那很瞧不起人
Yes, it was quite patronizing.
我觉得有点过分
I thought it was a bit too far, actually.
你非常聪明
You're very clever.
我知道
I know.
时间异体在一处旧犯罪现场留下了点东西
The Variant left something behind at an old crime scene.
一座大教堂  一个糖果盒
A cathedral. A candy box.
一个明显不符合时代的物件
An obvious anachronism.
我把它交给了分析师  但他们查不出什么
I gave it to Analysis, but they couldn't find anything real.
-这有什么关系  -因为现在有两个变量
- Why does that matter? - 'Cause now we have two variables.
天启级别的自然灾害
Apocalyptic natural disasters and...
爆炸蓝莓口香糖
-爆炸蓝莓  -那是什么
- Kablooie. - What's that?
糖果  阿斯加德有糖果吗
Candy. Do you have candy on Asgard?
有  葡萄  坚果
Yeah. Grapes, nuts.
怪不得你这么哀怨
No wonder you're so bitter.
好了  爆炸蓝莓只在地球特定地区有卖
Okay. Kablooie was only sold regionally on Earth
时间是从2047年到2051年
from 2047 to 2051.
我们只需要把它与所有天启事件交叉对照
All we gotta do is cross-reference that with every apocalyptic event.
我分你一半
I'm gonna give you half.
我们来比比看  谁先找到
And let's make it a competition, see who finds it, ok?
-好  -要赌点什么吗
- Sure. - You wanna bet something?
-好  -君子赌约
- Yeah. - Gentleman's bet.
为骄傲而战吧  祝最厉害的人取胜  开始
Yeah, let's play for pride. Okay. May the best man win. Go.
找到了吗
Anything?
不是2048年的气候灾害
It's not the climate disaster of 2048.
也不是2051年的海啸
Or the tsunami of 2051.
快  快  快
Let's go. Let's go. Come on.
2050年
2050.
燕子灭绝  是这个吗
The extinction of the swallow... Is that a thing?
彻底毁掉了生态系统
Completely screwed up the ecosystem.
印尼的喀拉喀托火山也在2049年喷发了
Krakatoa erupted in 2049 as well.
没有爆炸蓝莓
No Kablooie.
天啊  坏事一件接着一件  是不是
God, it's just one damn thing after another, isn't it?
-风暴  饥荒  火山  洪水  -找到了
- Cyclone, famine, volcanoes, floods... - Got him.
天启事件报告  阿拉巴马圣所山  2050年
-他就在这里  -阿拉巴马  2050年
- That's where he is. - Alabama, 2050.
要是我不留神  你可能会抢了我的工作
You're gonna take my job if I'm not careful.
你想让我批准
You want me to approve
派一支全副武装的特遣部队去...
deployment of a fully-armed task force to...
-对  -时间异体可能的藏匿处
- Yeah. - ...the Variant's potential hiding spot?
阿拉巴马圣所山
Haven Hills, Alabama,
曾是罗克斯卡特所有的企业镇
corporate town owned by Roxxcart
被一场飓风摧毁
until it's wiped out by a hurricane.
食物供给那里全都有
All the food and supplies you need.
如果他喜欢的话
If he likes it,
他完全可以一次次地回去
there's no reason he can't keep going back
在那里扎营
and just camping out, over and over.
你的依据就是一个让你上次任务失败的
And this is all based on a theory from the Variant
-时间异体提出的理论  -对  他做得很好
- who just blew your previous mission? - Yeah, he's doing great.
莫比乌斯  作为你的朋友
Mobius, as your friend,
我必须告诉你  相信这个人可不是明智之举
I have to tell you that trusting this man is not a good idea.
是啊  我知道  但也许他值得一试
No. I know. But maybe he's worth the trouble.
他发现了我们安保的一个巨大漏洞
He just uncovered a huge hole in our security.
我就是担心这个
That's what concerns me!
我能应付他  相信我
I can handle him. Trust me.
我们肯定能在这里抓住他
This is where we get our guy.
你  我信得过  但是他
You, I trust, but him.
听着  萝雯娜  我的直觉告诉我
Listen, Ravonna, every instinct is telling me
我们能在这里抓住时间异体
this is where we nail the Variant.
拜托  我这样激动可不多见  对不对
Come on. You don't see me usually this worked up, right?
我很兴奋
I'm excited.
我已经迫不及待了
I'm chomping at the bit.
-好吧  -好
- Okay. - Yes. Okay.
-但是莫比乌斯  -怎么了
- But, Mobius? - Yeah?
如果不成功的话  我就帮不了你了
There's not much I can do if it doesn't work out.
时时刻刻
For all time.
永永远远
Always.
好
Okay.
我们可以行动了
We're on.
我们今天要大干一场
We are doing some good work today.
我也这么想
I thought so too.
我跟你讲  你要是真帮我们抓到这个时间异体
I'm tellin' you. You actually help us catch this Variant,
谁知道会怎样呢  朋友
and who knows, my friend.
足以见到时间守护者吗
What, good enough for a face-to-face with the Time-Keepers?
我可没这么说
I didn't say that.
-一步一步来  -好  一步一步来
- One step at a time. - All right. One step at a time.
-以防万一  -嗯  这些真是...
- Just in case. - Yeah, don't those feel...
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
集合汇报情况
Gather around for a briefing.
罗克斯卡特是一个该时代典型的超级商场
Roxxcart is a vast superstore common to the era.
其中包含很多拓展区域
It consists of a series of sprawling sections,
还有一个很大的仓库
including a large warehouse.
平民们将这个仓库
This warehouse is being used by
当作风暴避难所
civilians as a shelter tryin' to ride out the storm.
记住  这是十级天启事件
Remember, this is a class ten apocalypse.
时间异体不该知道我们来了
While the Variant shouldn't know we're coming,
他可能躲在任何地方  我们应假定他有攻击性
he could be hiding anywhere and should be considered hostile.
所以保持警惕
So stay alert.
每次攻击  时间异体都会偷取重置设备
Every time there is an attack, the Variant steals a reset charge.
他肯定有什么计划
He's planning something.
我们只是还不知道是什么
We just don't know what.
留意那些消失的设备
So keep an eye out for the missing charges,
如果发现一个洛基  就删除
and if you see a Loki, prune it.
最好是删了坏的那个
The bad Loki, preferably.
阿拉巴马圣所山
罗克斯卡特
有发现吗
Anything?
还没有  继续搜
Nothing yet. Move out!
搞什么
The hell was that?
是我用魔法弄干了我的衣服
That was me using magic to dry my clothes.
这样我就不用像你们这样
So I don't announce myself
用湿嗒嗒的脚步声到处宣布自己的到来
with every squeaky footstep like the rest of you.
带上两支小队搜索风暴避难所
Take both teams and sweep the storm shelter.
-是  长官  -我和洛基
- Yes, ma'am. - Loki and I are gonna
去看看温室  我们到...
check out the Green House. We'll meet back at the...
-不行  -不行
- No. - No?
你跟D90走  他得跟我一起
You go with D-90. He stays with me.
你说什...他在我监管之下
What are you... He's under my supervision.
这是我的外勤行动  莫比乌斯
This is my field op, Mobius.
如果他没有威胁
If he's not a threat,
-那倒还...  -他当然有威胁
- then it won't be... - Of course he's a threat.
-还记得时间剧院吗  -莫比乌斯
- Remember the Time Theater? - Mobius...
所以他必须跟着我
That's why I want him with me.
你要是想回时管局
You are more than welcome to go back
向伦斯雷尔提起诉讼  随便你  但现在...
to the TVA and litigate with Renslayer, but right now...
我们都来了  我们不回去
We're here. We're not going back.
-时间异体就在这里  -莫比乌斯  没事的
- The Variant is here. - Mobius, it's fine. It's fine.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
我知道信任是要自己争取的  所以我会的
I understand I have to earn that, so, I will.
为什么不可信任的人倒很喜欢说"相信我"
Why is it the people you can't trust are always saying, "Trust me"?
行吧  这次可抓牢你的时间项圈
Okay, try to hang on to your Time Collar this time.
我们在陈列室会和
We'll see you in the showroom.
-很高兴我能和你单独相处  -安静
- I am glad we're getting to spend this time together. - Quiet.
我们一开始可能有误...
I'm saying we got off on the wrong...
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
买绿植
Shopping for plants.
在暴风雨里
In this storm?
飓风大减价呢
It's a hurricane sale.
杜鹃花半折
Azaleas are half off.
这人会是你吗
Could that be you?
我可能还是会穿西装  但有可能
I mean, I probably would have worn a suit, but, yes, maybe.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
没有  他们一般都会活下来的
No. They usually survive.
那么
So,
你就是时管局叫来追捕我的笨蛋
you're the fool the TVA brought in to hunt me down.
你  是我吧
Me, I presume.
拜托  如果要说  也是你是我
Please. If anyone's anyone, you're me.
见到你很高兴
How nice to meet you.
过去的一小时内  风越来越大
For the past hour we have seen winds intensifying.
如果你们调到...
Again, if you're just tuning in...
看看包里有没有重置设备
Check the bags for the reset charges.
你们是联邦应急管理署的吗
You guys FEMA?
还是国民警卫队
National Guard?
他们中任何人都有可能
Could be any one of them.
如果你们有直升机  或者其他交通工具
Well, hey, if you got a 'copter or other transport,
那就该拿出来了
now is the time to use it.
这里还有女人和小孩  这天气可不是开玩笑的
We got women and kids, and that weather ain't playin'.
很抱歉  我们没有
No, I'm sorry. We don't.
那你们怎么过来的
Well, how the heck did you get here?
你干什么
What are you doing?
这些人很害怕
These people are scared.
他们快死了  是该怕
They're about to die. They should be scared.
不该怕我们
Okay. Not of us.
-长官  -冷静点
- Sir! - Take it easy.
怎么了
What is it?
是真的  是真的  是真的
It's real. It's real. It's real.
魅术是个聪明的小把戏
Enchantment is a clever trick.
很怂包  有点业余  但很聪明
Cowardly, a bit amateur-ish, but clever.
几乎跟给时管局干活一样怂包
Almost as cowardly as working for the TVA.
我只为我自己干活
I'm working for me.
你真这么想吗
You really believe that, don't you?
没错
Yeah.
我还担心他们会发现一个更强的我呢
And here I was worried that they'd found a better version of me.
你们在找避难所吗
Hi, are you guys looking for the disaster shelter?
不是
No.
上帝保佑
Oh, bless.
你要叫你的小朋友们来帮忙吗
Are you going to call your little friends for help?
怎么了
What's the matter?
你不敢跟我面对面吗
You too scared to meet me face-to-face?
现身吧
Show yourself.
获得他们的信任绝非易事
You know, gaining their confidence was no mean feat.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是卧底
You went undercover.
如果你能暂时收起你的奉承话
If you could possibly sheathe your smarm for a moment,
我有个提议给你  所以我才来找你
I have an offer for you. That's why I found you.
说吧
Go on.
我要推翻时间守护者
I'm going to overthrow the Time-Keepers.
我把话挑明了
And, uh, cards on the table,
我需要一个够格的副手
I could use a qualified lieutenant.
我猜你说的是...我
And I assume you mean... Me?
你怎么说
What say you...
洛基
Loki?
别这么喊我
Don't call me that.
你可以叫我...
You can call me...
兰迪
Randy.
天啊  现在我明白托尔为何觉得这很烦人了
God. Now I understand why Thor found this so annoying.
听着  别再玩游戏了  我一直在帮你
Listen. Enough with your games. I've been trying to help you.
我在文艺复兴集会拖延了他们好一阵
I kept them vulnerable at the Renaissance Fair for some time.
天啊  你人真好
Oh, gosh, and that was just so nice of you.
但经过八到十秒钟的考虑后
But after eight to ten seconds of consideration,
我的回答是  不
the answer is no.
我没兴趣统治时间变异管理局
I'm not interested in ruling the Time Variance Authority.
是真的  是真的
It's real. It's real.
It was real. It was real.
-什么是真的  什么...  -是真的
- What's real? What's... - It's real.
-她疯了  -是真的
- She's off the dial. - It's real.
-看着我  -是真的
- Look at me. - It's real.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
我们会送你回家
We're gonna get you there.
联系时管局  通知医务室...
Call the TVA, let the infirmary know...
不不  我泄密了
No, no, no. I gave it away.
-我泄密了  -你泄了什么密
- I gave it away. - What did you give away...
时间守护者  他们的所在
The Time-Keepers, where they are.
我泄漏了找到他们的方法
I gave it away how to find them.
B15  你情况如何
B-15, what is your status?
B15  请回复  你情况如何
B-15, come in. What's your status?
B15  能收到吗
B-15, do you copy?
如果你不想统治时管局  那你想要什么
If you don't wanna rule the TVA, then what do you want?
不重要  你来得太迟了
It doesn't matter. You're too late.
我想你会发现我是来得早才对
I think you'll find I'm well ahead of schedule.
我弹指间就找到了你的藏身处
I found your hiding place like that.
所以我是更厉害的洛基  你同意吗
I'd say that makes me the superior Loki, wouldn't you?
原来如此  这就是你的计划
I see. That's your plan.
把我们全引来这里  好炸毁这地方
Lure us all here so you can blow the place up.
我想兰迪了
I miss Randy.
谢谢你帮我拖延时间
Thank you for helping me stall for time.
你真的很喜欢听自己说话
You really do love to hear yourself talk.
你是第一个跟我说这话的人
You're the first person to tell me that.
什么
What?
我绝不会这样对待我
I would never treat me like this.
出来啊  别躲了
Oh, come on. Stop hiding.
洛基  如果你有自尊  就用真身和我打
Loki, if you had any honor you'd fight me as yourself.
谁理你啊
I have shit to do.
-莫比乌斯  -他在哪
- Mobius. - Where is he?
-我跟丢他了  -发生了什么
- I lost him. - What happened?
我...
I...
看来你最喜欢的洛基背叛你了  莫比乌斯
Looks like your favorite Loki betrayed you, Mobius.
快走
Just move!
你想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
这是怎么回事
What is this about?
做好准备  洛基
Brace yourself, Loki.
你想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
这是怎么回事
What is this about?
你想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
这是怎么回事
What is this about?
你想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
这是怎么回事
What is this about?
这与你无关
This isn't about you.
好吧
Right.
启动
正在初始化
它们去哪了
Where they going?
这不可能
That's not possible.
我是分析师1182E  报告代码000
This is Analyst 1182-E, uh, reporting a code, uh, 000.
多个时间分支快速出现  斜率为...
Branches rapidly forming at a slope...
有人刚炸了神圣时间线
Somebody just bombed the Sacred Timeline.
洛基
Loki!
洛基  等等
Loki, wait!
等等  洛基  等一下
Wait! Loki, wait!
不  等等  洛基
No! Wait, Loki!
该死
Damn it!